Contacts

Date of birth 06.12.1989

City Vilnius

Phone +370 602 902 14

E-mail egle.ct@gmail.com

About me

I am a beginner web developer who is looking forward to new challenges in programming and automation area. Before I developed an interest for coding, I was an experienced IT Service Desk support analyst at *Danske Bank Group IT Lithuania* for over 2 years. In order to re-establish myself as a developer, I have completed intensive programming courses for beginners at Vilnius Coding School and then PHP courses at Code Academy. To better understand IT infrastructure, I have obtained knowledge and certificate of ITIL, in addition, I had an opportunity to cover a Queue Manager role in Application Integration team within Danske Bank for 3 months. To sum up, I have a keen interest in computer science, knowledge about IT infrastructure, great communication skills, I understand the value of good service objectives and I am excited for new opportunities within IT world.

Education

01.09.2009 - 30.06.2013

English Philology and German Language (Bachelor degree) at Šiauliai University

01.04 - 30.07 / 2012

English Philology and German Language University of Hildesheim

Trainings

20.12.2017 - 26.01.2018

PHP courses at Code Academy

26.10 - 13.12 / 2016

Programming courses for beginners (introduction to C#, Java, JS, HTML, CSS and MySQL) at Vilnius Coding School

07-09.11.2016

Windows 10 Client: New Features and Upgrade (Danske Bank)

16-18.08.2016

ITIL Foundation (Danske Bank)

01.10 - 01.11 / 2014

Evening language program (German) at University of Westminster, London, UK

Skills

HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP

JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY

PHP, MYSQL

WORDPRESS, GITHUB, SEO, SASS

Tools

Service Management & Collaboration platforms:

Service Now, Service Manager 9.4, Trello

Mailing systems:

Lotus Notes, MS Outlook

Code Editors:

Visual Studio Code, Atom, Sublime Text

FTP Clients:

WinSCP, FileZilla 3.33.0

Languages	Speaking	Understanding	Writing
English	Perfect	Perfect	Perfect
German	Average	Average	Average

Native Lithuanian

Work experience

since 01.02.2018

Freelance Web Developer at www.visuallab.lt

18.05.2015 - 01.09.2017

IT Service Desk support analyst at Danske Bank Group IT Lithuania DGITL 01.03 - 01.06 / 2017 Temporary positioned as Queue Manager in Application Integration team within Danske Bank.

13.01.2014 - 01.03.2015

Lounge catering staff at Institute of Directors, London, UK.